Contact

rebecht30@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rachelbecht-4413a8b8 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare
Patient Safety
Nursing

Rachel Becht

Nurse Manager - Green Emergency Department at Cleveland Clinic Akron General

Doylestown

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Patient Satisfaction, Lean Six Sigma, Customer Service, Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional graduated from The University of Akron (BSN) and Walsh University (MBA)

Experience

Cleveland Clinic Akron General Nurse Manager - Green Emergency Department May 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months) Uniontown, Ohio

University Hospitals Assistant Nurse Manager - ED June 2018 - May 2019 (1 year) Cleveland, Ohio

Summa Health 13 years

Unit Director - Surgical Trauma ICU June 2017 - June 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Akron, Ohio

Unit Director, 2 East ~ Women's Health March 2016 - June 2017 (1 year 4 months) Akron

RN Clinical Coordinator, PACU March 2015 - March 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Registered Nurse July 2005 - March 2015 (9 years 9 months)

Education

Walsh University

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Health/Health Care Administration/ Management · (2017 - 2019)

The University of Akron Bachelor's of Nursing